[PULSING DARK SYNTH
MUSIC PLAYING]
[WISTFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Scientists like Albert Einstein
highlight imagination as crucial
for scientific leaps.
He even said,
"Imagination is more important
than knowledge."
And in times like this,
imagination is the only thing
that can save me.
[BODY THUDS]
[ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[REFLECTIVE SYNTH
MUSIC PLAYING]
[BROODING ELECTRONIC
[MCKENNA] Thank you for coming,
and I'll try to be very brief.
I'm McKenna Manalo,
Principal of Omni-Stan.
[LAUGHING]
Your name is McKenna?
[LAUGHS]
- It doesn't really suit you.
- Grandma.
- Excuse me?
- Oh... Nothing, ma'am.
- You may proceed.
- Okay.
- [GRACE] Oh... Principal.
- Yes?
Personally...
I want to apologize for what
my daughter, Dessalyn, did.
It's Daphne, Ma.
Daphne.
Shut up with the "Daphne" crap!
You keep insisting
on being called Daphne,
but look at the shameful things
you've been up to!
- Shh! [CLICK TONGUE]
- Oh! But it's true!
I don't understand what's gotten
into my daughter either.
We raised her properly,
didn't we?
But sometimes,
we just can't control her.
- She can be so moody, too!
- Ma! Ma, stop it.
- It's true!
- [VICTOR] Principal McKenna.
I know my daughter.
She's kind and
she sees the good in people.
If she made a mistake,
I'm sure...
she didn't mean to.
I just want to know
[HELEN] Oh, ma'am!
Ma'am.
I'm Isobel's grandma.
I just wanna know,
why are we here?
Those are very good questions,
- and I will answer them all.
- I'll tell you later, grandma.
But first, we are here today
because...
nude photos of your daughters
have been leaked
all over the school.
And our IT Department
has already deleted
all the uploaded photos,
and they will continuously
do so,
whenever someone uploads any.
While we've contained it
for now,
some copies have already
been saved and shared.
That's why we're requesting
a media blackout.
Young ladies should not
act this way!
What happened to the
values this school instills?
Like modesty, self-respect,
and purity.
Like you, Ms. Briones,
top of her batch.
Your records are clean.
You're the most
well-behaved student.
What happened?
Point taken, Principal.
My daughter is kind.
You may continue.
Okay.
The school board of directors
was pushing to have
your daughters expelled.
[GASPS]
- What?
- Oh no.
- They're being expelled?
- Yes, initially.
I managed to bargain with them
because your kids
are gifted students.
It'd be a shame!
And so, in the meantime,
you, young ladies...
- ...are all suspended.
- What?!
- Dad, that's too much...
- That's the solution?
To suspend the kids?
Principal McKenna...
I'm sorry I don't mean to argue,
but with all due respect...
Shouldn't the boys
be the ones suspended?
And which boys are you
referring to, Ms. Briones?
Why would I suspend them?
Our boyfriends...
...because they're the ones
who leaked our photos.
Cole, Ant, Lester.
You have to stop right there.
Let's not be quick to accuse
other people.
And I guarantee you...
...that my son,
my dearest Lester,
doesn't have anything
to do with the scandal.
In fact,
he's only getting dragged
because one of you
is saying he's involved in this.
- [MARLA] But Principal--
- Marla.
Let the adults talk.
Principal McKenna...
Photos don't just spread
on their own
if no one uploads them.
And no photos
would've been leaked...
...if no one sent them,
Mrs. Briones.
Even if someone
sends the photos,
the other party has no right
to share it, Mrs. Manalo.
You should be investigating
who leaked
the kids' nude photos.
Marla, what law covers this?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
We can file a criminal case
for the violation
of Republic Act No. 9995...
Or the Anti-Photo and Video
Voyeurism Act of 2009.
This goes against the people
who have shared
or leaked nudes without consent.
It can also fall
under Republic Act No. 10175,
the Cybercrime Prevention Act
of 2012.
This is for cyber libel
and illegal access.
I know that, too.
- Oh, come on.
- You're late.
[MCKENNA] Does everybody share
the same feelings?
Does anyone want to file a case?
Hey? Let's do it.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Well, this is a free country,
and you can easily do so,
Mrs. Briones.
But doing so might lead
to a more catastrophic result.
Are you sure
no one will question
what kind of mother you are
to your daughter?
It might ruin
your family's reputation!
Mr. Rodriguez,
an unconventional family.
Two fathers raising
an adopted daughter.
Can two men raise
a child properly?
The LGBTQIA+ community
might even get questioned
because of your negligence.
I'm here to protect
your children.
Because I don't want them
to suffer
from further humiliation.
So why are you still going
to publicize this?
Right? It's unfair to the kids.
Don't worry because I believe
that you're right.
What?
- It's our child's fault!
- Mom...
- Shh!
- Besides, we don't have money
for all those lawsuits.
What kind of woman are you, huh?
If you wanted to strip,
you should've just
- auditioned for a film.
- Mom, come on.
- At least you'd get paid.
- Stop, Mom.
Did something happen
to my grandchild?
Your daughters...
...are suspended for five days.
All of this will be reflected
in your children's records.
They will not be eligible
for any honors,
internships, or awards
until further notice.
The meeting is over.
Thank you very much.
- I have a question!
- What? Why?
[LIGHTS BOOMING OFF]
Who are we going to ask
about this?
- What's that?
- Principal McKenna?
Are you not paying
the electricity bill?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
- Oh my god!
- [DOOR THUDS]
You scared me!
April, how long are you going
to avoid me?
April! April!
April, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Migo...
What part of "break"
don't you understand?
I don't get
what "break" means.
Ah! I break any code,
hack any tech, but this...
You...
I don't get you.
This has been going on
for almost a month now, April.
[MIGO SIGHS]
When are you going
to give me a clear answer?
April!
April! Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What do you wanna hear then?
[MIGO GROANS SOFTLY]
April, I want the truth!
That's all I want to know.
Migo...
I'm just not...
...sure about you anymore.
Okay?
It's like-- Okay.
I'm a computer whiz,
and so are you.
And everybody seems to be,
what? Rooting for us?
Because we like computer stuff?
And video games?
But that's all we ever do.
That's not the only thing we do.
- I'm not joking with you.
- Me too!
[MIGO CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Do I look like
I'm playing with you?
Look.
I'm just not sure about you.
I'm not sure about us.
I don't know
if I still love you.
[APRIL SIGHS]
That's why I asked
for a break up.
I'm sorry.
Well, did I agree
that we break up?
I don't need your permission.
[MIGO CHUCKLES]
April, there are two of us
in this relationship.
You can't be the only one
making decisions.
Migo, you're getting
on my nerves.
[MIGO CHUCKLES]
Is this a prank?!
This is a prank!
Where are the hidden cameras?
This is not a prank!
Why can't you just accept it?!
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Migo...
please...
Let me go.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know...
Leaking nudes is really common
these days.
You wouldn't even dare.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MIGO CHUCKLING]
So you're threatening me now?
Is this what you call love?
Huh, Migo?
[APRIL INHALES]
Why? Why would you go this far?
[APRIL CRIES SOFTLY]
And then you'll wonder
why I don't want you anymore.
Did you really think, Migo...
...that I'd go back to you
just because you threatened me?
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do you think...
I would want to be with you...
when you're...
...when you're literally
scaring me?
A-April, I'm so sorry,
I didn't mean to.
I don't think I can be okay
without you, April.
April, I love you so much.
Please.
Migo...
I don't care...
...if you release my nudes.
I can always say it's AI.
Now, Migo,
if you really love me...
and if you still have
any respect for me...
Let me go.
Please, April...
Don't leave me.
- Please, April. Please...
- I'm sorry.
- Goodbye, Migo.
- Just give me a chance.
April!
You'll come back to me!
Just watch me!
You'll come back! April!
[KICK LANDS]
[MIGO CRYING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[BODIES THUD]
April...
Are you okay?
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
Mm-hmm.
I have to go.
I'm gonna be late
for my chemical peel.
Mom! Wait!
Aren't we even
gonna do anything?
What? You're suspended, right?
But aren't we filing a case?
[SIGHS]
We don't have any evidence yet.
Besides, McKenna's right.
Even if she looks
like Goldilocks.
The photos will
just spread more.
Filing a case is a long process.
Even my annulment case
with your dad
still hasn't gone anywhere.
You are responsible...
...for whatever you send
out there.
I really thought
you knew better.
All your hard work, poof!
Gone! Down the drain!
Just because you played dumb.
If there's anything
that I wanted you to learn
from when your father left us,
it's not to be as stupid
as I was.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Like mother, like daughter.
[MARLA SNIFFLES]
Mom...
- Hm! Oh!
- I'm sorry.
Don't...
Don't drop that tear.
Don't show that you're affected.
The least you can do is...
Be proud of it.
- Be proud of your nude photos!
- Mom!
How can I be proud
of my nude photos?
My life is ruined!
[MARLA SNIFFLING]
This is so embarrassing.
It's really embarrassing,
but don't show it.
Don't give them the luxury
of showing your tears.
Hm.
Hold your head up.
Hm. Show your chin.
Don't drop that tear,
don't drop that.
And then smile.
Smile some more.
- Smile.
- Mom?
People are already staring
at us. Do it!
[BELL RINGING]
Smile. There you go.
Now, laugh.
[LAUGHING FORCEFULLY]
Scandal?
Are you bothered?
Me? Bothered? No.
[LAUGHING FORCEFULLY]
Louder!
I'll just move on.
[LAUGHING FORCEFULLY]
Thank you! Thank God!
- You, young lady!
- Mom! That hurts!
- You're becoming too much.
- [PHONE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hey, hey.
Who was that? Was it Lester?
Why didn't you answer him?
I don't want to talk to him!
- Dear...
- Oh?
Tsk! Was that you?
It smells bad.
Ah! No!
Why didn't you answer him?!
Where else will you find
a good guy?
He's smart, kind,
and, most importantly, rich!
He's our ticket
out of poverty, right?
Mom, I can do that myself!
I'll do even better in school!
I'll be able to study abroad!
I'll find a good job
that pays well!
- We don't need Lester!
- Grace...
Did I say you could talk?
Dessalyn, first of all,
being smart won't get you
ahead in life.
Okay? What, you're going abroad?
You'll work?
But in the end,
it's still a man
who'll carry you through life!
When you fall in love,
you get married.
When you get married,
you'll have kids,
and then you'll have a family.
So where will you use
your diploma by then?
Nowhere, right?
Use your brain, not just books!
- Mom. Mom! Mom!
- Shhh!
Don't you trust me?
I can do it!
Look at your father.
He finished law school, right?
But he still can't pass
the bar exam.
We didn't get anything
out of it.
And now,
he's addicted to gambling,
and we're buried in debt.
See?! Your father is no use
to us!
[SNEEZES]
- It's like--
- Excuse me, excuse me.
You got something to say?
Dessa, I don't earn enough
for all of us.
We're already using your stipend
to pay the electricity bill.
And now,
you're getting suspenders?
"Suspenders"? It's "suspended"!
It's the same thing!
Well, you're suspended,
so what do we do now?
I'll handle it. I'll find a way!
You should! So call Lester now.
Talk to each other!
I don't care about
those nude photos anymore!
First of all,
people will forget about that,
and something new will come up.
The new thing will get
all the attention.
Besides, you're not
a celebrity or famous person,
so stop overreacting!
Tsk. Mm...
What-- What's your name again?
Daisy?
Daphne! Daphne!
Daphne?
Make sure you use Daphne
to the best of your ability.
I'm taking back
what I said earlier.
Let's go.
Coming.
Dear, I'm sorry
I couldn't defend you
against your mom.
I understand, Dad.
I'm sorry you got dragged
into this mess.
It's okay.
The important thing is,
follow what your heart wants--
Sounds like
you're saying something.
Are you talking about me?
- Nothing...
- No, we're not.
Yes! No! Yes!
Why are your eyes so big?
Are you mad at me?
- Are you angry?
- No. Yes.
What were you saying about me?
- You've got some nerve!
- I said nothing!
See! This is what
I was telling you.
- I'm not-- I'm not mad.
- Yes, you are.
That's enough.
Settle that at home.
What do you mean I'm raising
my voice? It's my norm--
That's not true!
This is just who I am!
Dad, I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry, Dad.
[NYX CRYING]
Stop saying sorry.
It's not your fault.
I'm not angry.
I'm so ashamed
to face you and Dada.
[NYX CRYING]
I'm so ashamed.
I know the sacrifices...
...you made just to get me
into SOSH.
You might think I'm taking
your hard work for granted,
but that's not it.
This is annoying
and embarrassing.
I'm just adopted,
and yet I act like this.
Adopted?
Who told you that?
Did you read my diary?!
[NYX] Dad, that's too loud.
Dad, I already know.
You're not adopted.
You're my daughter.
[SIGHS]
My baby.
You're our baby, mine and Dad's.
I don't want to hear
that again, okay?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't know how...
I don't even know how
to face you anymore
because...
I know...
you think differently of me now.
I'm really sorry, Dad.
I promise, I'll really do
my best no matter what.
I'll make you proud
of me again, I promise.
- Promise.
- My daughter, listen to me.
This doesn't change
how I see you.
Your Dad and I...
we are so proud of you.
We even brag about you
at the salon.
To our gay and middle-aged
women customers.
Future Bill Gates
and Steve Jobs, right?
[CHUCKLES]
[CRYING]
But, Nyx...
I hope you're careful about
who you choose to love.
Don't confuse attention...
with connection.
Or worse...
love.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CRYING] Dad...
You're pretty good at these
words of wisdom, Dad.
Stop crying.
[VICTOR] Want me
to shave their heads?
No, Dad.
Dad, hey!
What are you doing, Dad? Hey!
Dad, what are you doing?!
Dad! What are you doi--
Dad!
Dad, for the love of Beyonce,
what are you doing, Dad?!
I'm standing by you.
If you feel like they're
stripping you bare
then I want you to know
I'm right here with you.
Naked?
[VICTOR] That I'm with you
and I'm protecting you.
They can look at your body
but not your soul.
So they can feast at my body.
Dad...
I appreciate
the statement effect.
I loved your campy performance.
Thank you, but...
that'll only make things
harder for me at school.
Let's keep you dressed up.
Fine. It's embarrassing.
[NYX] Right, a little bit...
Put your belt back on,
that's expensive.
Close that.
Dad, please don't.
Dad, they will see
your wild side.
[WIND CHIMES CLINKING]
[BAG THUDS]
[LINE BEEPS]
[ISOBEL'S DAD] What am I hearing
about a scandal?
You know what, I don't
even want to know.
I don't have time for this.
You're grown now.
You can take care of yourself.
I won't be able to go home
to visit Mom.
Take care of your grandma, okay?
I'll just send money.
Remember, Isobel, you're
responsible for your Grandma.
Her life is in your hands.
So, please, behave yourself.
Don't get involved
in any scandals.
[LINE BEEPS]
[ISOBEL'S MOM] Isobel,
I'm sorry if I can't be there.
I can't come home.
You know how it is,
Gavin's starting school,
and your Stepdad Fred...
he won't let me because no one
will be left to handle things.
I'm the only one managing
the business here in Canada.
Honey, why did you send
nude photos?
You should've thought about
Grandma Helen.
You're all she has now.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[METAL THUDS]
[HELEN] Isobel.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[HAMMER THUDS]
Let's eat now, dear.
[HELEN] Let's eat together.
[HELMET THUDS]
So we can watch
K-Drama later, okay?
And then, tomorrow I'll go
with you to your school.
Why are we being called to
the principal’s office?
What happened?
Did someone bother you?
[GASPS]
There’s a lot of mess, dear.
I'll clean it up later, Grandma.
[HELEN] Yes, you should.
Ah...
What was I saying again?
- Why am I here again?
- Ah...
You were asking me
to eat inside...
- Isobel
- But don't worry, Grandma,
I'll clean it up later.
I'll go ahead.
Remember
If there's a mess,
you need to clean it up.
- [MUSIC STINGS]
- [ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARLA] When something
unpredictable occurs,
I rely on my own theories
to explain why it happened.
These theories are based
on facts that are
repeatedly confirmed by
observation and experimentation.
It needs to make sense to me,
but what happens when suddenly,
the facts start to blur
and become a lie
[ETHEREAL MUSIC
CONTINUES, FADES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[MARLA] Cole.
[COLE] Marla,
what are you doing here?
It's already late.
I want to talk to you.
I was actually gonna go
to your place.
Why?
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Why did you leak my photos?
I thought I could trust you.
Marla
I'm not the one
who leaked your photos.
[COLE] I don’t know
how that happened.
I had nothing to do with it.
Promise,
Somebody probably hacked
my phone.
I don't believe you.
- [MARLA] You're lying.
- No.
What about Isobel?
[COLE] What about Isobel?
You've cheated on me
with Isobel.
[COLE] Marla, come on.
You know Isobel, right?
You know her really well.
She's just seeking attention.
And that girl's crazy.
She's a weirdo.
You two are enemies, right?
- Marla?
- Please, please...
Please!
Stop lying to me, Cole.
Please stop lying to me.
I thought I knew you.
But right now, it's like
I don't know you at all.
There's this other side
that I've never seen and
I don't know
who you are anymore.
Marla, what are you saying?
I'm still the same Cole
you grew up with.
Why don't you believe me?
Marla...
I'm not the one
who leaked the photos.
Please, believe me.
And I never cheated on you!
I'm sorry that this is
happening to you now.
But I just want you to know
that I'm here,
supporting you
But, no.
You just won’t believe me.
What can I do?
Maybe
you just need some time alone.
What? What?
Cole.
What do you mean? What?
What are you trying to say?
You wanna know?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you even know what I had to
sacrifice just to be with you?
Do you know I’m willing
to fight for you?
Do you know that if Dad
finds out what happened to you,
I’ll be the one
he goes after again?
I’m the one he’ll end up
hitting again.
- Sorry.
- You know Dad, right?
- I'm sorry.
- He doesn’t want
our names dragged
into a scandal.
But I’m choosing you, Marla.
I'm choosing you.
I choose you.
And I’m risking
everything for you,
still, I'm the bad one.
- That's unfair, Marla.
- No...
No.
I've already explained myself.
So, what's the point?
What's the point?
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry. [CRYING]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. No.
Please, I'm
I'm just so confused.
Please. I'm just so confused.
And I don't understand
anything that's happening.
Please don't leave me.
Please. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- Please.
- Marla...
Please, please, please.
Please, please.
I get it,
hurt people hurt people.
But I just can’t imagine
being with someone
who chooses not to believe me.
What kind of girlfriend are you?
That’s non-negotiable for me.
After everything,
you still don’t trust me?
We’ve known each other
for so long.
Since we were kids, Marla.
No, no.
It's my fault.
I'm wrong.
You're right, I'm wrong.
Please.
Just don't leave me, please.
I need you so much right now.
Please don't leave me.
Please, please.
Think about what I’m
going through too, Marla.
Not just you all the time.
[CRYING]
I always need to explain
things to you.
I explain everything.
You don't even listen to me.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Please.
- [MARLA] Please, please.
- [COLE] Don't.
[MARLA CRYING] No.
No, don't do this.
Please, please.
[CRYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Chaos theory teaches us to
expect the unexpected.
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
The butterfly effect highlights
how a butterfly flapping
its wings in New Mexico
can cause a hurricane in China.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
This shows how a small,
almost negligible event
can completely change
a person’s life.
When I sent my nudes to Cole,
I didn’t know that it would
eventually lead to our breakup.
[PENSIVE AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
[ALARM BEEPING]
That small event led
to drastic changes.
And the fallout
isn’t even over yet.
[ALARM BEEPING CONTINUOUSLY]
[PENSIVE AMBIENT MUSIC
CONTINUES]
[MARLA CLEARS THROAT]
Isobel, you bitch!
You look like shit.
Smell like shit, too.
You have a lot of nerve
coming here
after sleeping
with my boyfriend.
Would it make you
feel better if I told you
that Cole only wanted
to sleep with me,
but never loved me?
I don't know.
What are you doing here?
Of all the people
who could visit me,
it had to be you?
What do you want?
Someone told me, I should
clean up after my mess.
So you came here to apologize?
No.
How dare you.
I don't apologize for the things
I'm not ready to be sorry for.
Especially if the
outcome benefited us.
You found out that
your boyfriend is a cheat.
And...
a horrible person.
You also think
that he's responsible
for the leakage of our nudes.
I believe you.
But even if we find
some kind of proof,
that he's the who did it,
filing a case is not an option.
Marla, you know his father.
And you know the justice
system of this country.
So, do you want me
to be thankful?
Do you want me to say thank you
for believing in me?
Huh?
What do you want from me?
Do you want me to plot
some kind of revenge?
Your words.
Not mine.
Ugh!
You're unbelievable.
What-- what do you want
from me?!
Do you wanna see
how shitty I look?
how miserable I am? [SOBBING]
Or how much I've fallen
from grace? What?!
I never knew that Marla Briones
can raise her voice like that.
[APPLAUDING]
So feisty.
Or did you come here to ask
if Cole and I have broken up?
I know that's what
you wanna know!
Well, news flash!
He broke up with me!
I know you're happy
to hear that.
- I hate him!
- I hate him, too!
[SOBBING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[DOOR SLAMS OPEN]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Leave.
Get out!
I'm here because you need
my help.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Why would I ever need your help?
We should work together.
To get back at him.
You said revenge, right?
Don't you wanna know
the truth behind the leakage?
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
Don’t you want to see the people
who blamed us, pay the price?
We got suspended over
something out of our control,
yet we're the ones
being punished.
How are you handling everything?
Not so good,
obviously.
The real suspects are out there,
probably celebrating
while we face ridicule
and you know I hate
looking pathetic, Marla.
The only way to seek justice
is on our own terms.
And I know you hate me, too.
But guess what?
We have bigger fish to fry.
And frankly,
I'm the only one you
can trust right now.
What makes you say that?
Because I know exactly
what you're going through.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Revenge
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
I think we need reinforcements.
[DOOR CLOSES]
- [DIGITAL TRILL]
- Oh, shit!
I thought you were a demon.
Oops!
Why are you two together?
Are you friends now?
Is this a slumber party?
[SIGHS]
Marla,
aren't we supposed
to be mad at side chicks?
Don't worry,
we still hate side pieces.
But I can set aside my problems
for more important matters.
[CHUCKLES]
Speaking of important,
just a disclaimer,
excuse my language
but what the hell, girl?!
My nervous system
is all hyped up!
I like this kind of energy.
This is very exciting, like,
I'm very ecstatic.
Ecstatic?!
So fun! It's like
we're a girl group.
Hey... Hold on. Let's start.
What do we need to talk about?
[ISOBEL] In Marla's words,
our plan of revenge.
- Revenge?
- Yes, revenge!
- Are you deaf?!
- Hey, I didn't agree to that.
It was your idea anyway.
Why are we all here again?
I'm here because I want
to know the truth.
We all know that we're all
connected
to Cole, Lester, and Ant.
And all of us sent nude photos
to them.
You don't know that.
Don't jump to a conclusion
without a hypothesis, Marla.
It's a basic step, right?
[MARLA] Isobel, I don't need
to hypothesize
something that's already given.
- What's given?
- That you're a sidepiece.
- Oh!
- Burn.
- Burn...
- He liked it.
- Okay.
- It's getting too intense.
Yes, mhm.
I think we need an icebreaker.
Nyx! Nyx! Wait!
You talk too much.
Marla, are you saying
you want to find out
who leaked the photos?
- Yes!
- That’s it. It's that simple.
Yes, exactly.
That's what I want.
I'm sure we're all suspecting
Cole, Lester, and Ant.
[NYX] Okay, hold on.
Baby, hold on.
Hold onto that thought.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Um... [CLICKS TONGUE]
I know that...
it's easy to put
the blame on them,
but we can't just point
our fingers carelessly.
And one more thing,
my baby Nugnug won't do that.
[CHUCKLES] Sorry.
He really won't.
I like the optimism.
But you're not quite there yet.
Where?
[ISOBEL] Not here, obviously.
The thing is,
you should know they
have our nude photos.
Like your Nugnug.
But why would they do that?
Nugnug.
- Ask your Nugnug.
- Nyx...
that’s exactly
what I want to know.
That's why we're all here.
I want to know if what
I’m suspecting is true.
Then, how will we prove...
all your suspicions?
We need the help
of April Javier.
- [GRUNTS]
- Are you okay?
Huh? Hey.
Hey, girl.
Wait a minute.
April is Cole's twin.
Right?
I thought you wanted
to know the truth
and then you're just gonna
ask his sister for help?
Do you even know
the probability of success
if you bring April into this?
Oh, she's going off.
- She's being possessed!
- [WHEEZES]
Girl!
It's only at 2%, Marla.
Hello?!
I don't know how the heck
you came up
with that result, Dessalyn.
Hey!
Damn you. You've been at it.
What?!
-You just don't know how to sh--
- [MARLA] Girls!
Inside voices!
I don't care if you think
we need April.
We just need her on our side
to help kill her brother.
- Oh my!
- No.
- Told you. She's crazy!
- No, no, no...
- Huh?
- This girl is crazy.
I'm just kidding!
Of course, we'll torture
them first.
- Huh?
- Oh, a masochist.
She's a masochist.
- Who hurt you?
- I'm just kidding again!
She's into killing.
Don't you have a sense of humor?
You're supposed to laugh!
[FAKE LAUGHS]
'Cause it seems like
you're not joking, sis.
We can't trust her.
Blood...
will always
- You can do it!
- Blood will always be
thicker than water.
And!
And why her? Of all people?
- Girl, come on?
- Because she's a computer whiz.
We need her.
She can hack into any gadget,
any tablet, any device,
email, whatever account,
she can do it!
Why don't you do it?
Don't you claim to be a
photographic memory genius
of some sort?
Why can't you?
Because I'm not an expert
in application.
That's different.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I don't...
get where you're going
with this.
But I think, your plan,
it's too dangerous.
I don’t know what I want
to happen.
In fact, for the first time
in my life
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I feel like I don't know
anything.
All I know for a fact,
is we're all victims here.
And we all deserve
to know the truth.
Don't you want to know
if they did it?
If it was Cole, Lester, and Ant?
And if they did, my God,
they don't deserve us.
Nyx...
is it okay to you
that your boyfriend's...
a monster?
Fine. I'm down.
Whatever the plan is, I’m down.
I'm in.
Obviously.
This whole time.
I just need to...
do something... before I give...
my final answer... to your...
question.
Just one.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Power outage!
- Anthony!
- Nyx! What's this about?
Just come with me.
I didn't dress up like this
for you to ignore me.
Let's go!
- Come here.
- Nyx!
Come here!
Nyx, what's your problem?
We're not supposed to be here.
You're not supposed to be here!
And what's with that outfit?
Nugnug...
Why are you ignoring me?
You're not answering
my calls
and you leave me
on read.
Don't you want me anymore?
Just when I'm going
through something,
you make me feel you're
not there for me.
[NYX SIGHS]
Okay.
Nyx, I'm sorry.
I just feel like
having me around
only adds to your problem.
So, what now?
You're saying it's over?
Just say it.
I'm not going
to force you.
Thank you, nugget.
I know you'll understand me.
Hey!
That was a joke.
I was playing hard to get.
At least fight for me.
Get it?
Don't just leave me, Ant.
Nyx...
Having me around won't help you
move on from this incident.
I think it's best
if we break up.
Uh...
Say that again.
Repeat what you said.
Having me around
won't help you move on--
No, not that.
Fast forward.
Having me around won't help you
move on from this incident.
- Listen.
- No.
After that.
Having me around won't help you
move on from this incident.
I think it's best
if we break up.
Pause.
You're breaking up with me?!
Okay, fine.
Okay, not a breakup.
Cool off.
Wow, thank you.
- Nugnug, we need--
- Hold on.
Were you the one
who leaked my nudes?
Nyx...
I did not leak your nudes.
In the first place, I didn't
even ask for your nudes.
I thought you'd like
the pictures.
Well, it wasn't my idea.
Yeah, it was my idea.
It was my idea
to send the pictures.
You know why?
Because I felt like...
if I did that...
maybe you'd like me too.
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
Maybe you'd fall in love
with me, too.
Every time we kiss...
it feels like you're
just forcing it.
I thought that if I sent
you those pictures...
you'd find me pretty...
and fall in love
with me.
I don't feel like...
you like me the way
I like you.
Because, Ant...
I'm so into you.
A lot.
Isn't it obvious?
Nyx, since we're
already here,
I'm going to be transparent
with you.
My father is a pastor.
And he knows
about your scandal.
He doesn't want my reputation
to be affected
because that would
also affect
the reputation
of the whole church.
Nyx, you're a walking
oil spill right now.
It's spreading
like crazy,
and it's getting hard
to keep the water clean.
I just really feel like
we should break up.
It's for the best.
This will help us.
It's only temporary, okay?
Nyx, I know you understand
the situation.
Okay?
Wow.
Your timing is really
something.
You're really leaving me
right now, Ant?
- Really?
- Nyx...
I'm really, really sorry.
Okay?
Ant, please.
Don't leave me.
Nyx.
Nugnug.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WHIMPERS]
Nugget!
- [THUDS]
- [YELPS]
What the hell?!
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay.
There, there, there.
There, there!
Perfect.
This is the perfect hideout
in the school, right?
No.
You sure?
Gosh!
This place is such a mess.
It's so filthy.
This is okay.
I think we can make this work.
But, actually...
We don't need a secret hideout.
We don't have any use
for this anyway.
Hey.
You'll never know.
We might need a place
to hang out
when we want to appear
or disappear in school.
Right?
So, does that mean
you're with us, Nyx?
Yeah.
Ant just broke up
with me earlier.
Now, I just want the whole truth
and nothing but the truth.
So help me, Beyonce.
Okay.
First order of business.
[THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
How do we get April Javier
to say yes to helping us?
Can't we just ask her?
No, no.
It won't be that easy.
April is anti-social.
Plus, I know she doesn't
like Marla.
April dislikes a lot of people.
Like you.
And especially you.
- I don't care.
- Oh.
Then, I'll ask her.
I mean, you know me,
guys.
I'm friendly.
I hate to break it
to you, Nyx,
but sometimes, you can be
a little too loud.
April doesn't like loud.
Oh, really?
Is it April who doesn't
like it, or is it you?
Whatever.
Girls, focus.
We can't just ask her
to join us.
Sometimes,
the best plans can come
from the core principles.
- Core principles?
I have an idea.
[LIGHT DINGS]
- Oh my!
- Oh my god!
- You're overreacting!
- Newton's Three Laws of Motion.
First law.
An object will remain
in its state of motion
unless acted upon
by an external force.
Also known as...
inertia.
Oh. I like that kind
of drama.
I love it, I love it. Go.
But what's this external force?
And what is its connection
to Newton's Laws of Motion?
[ISOBEL] External force?
Let's use external force.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Stay still, you little bitch!
- [APRIL WHIMPERING]
- [THWACKING]
- [APRIL SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[APRIL, MUFFLED] Isobel!
[ISOBEL GRUNTS]
[MUFFLED] Let me go!
I'll poison you!
I'll pull out your hair!
And I'll kill all of your pets!
And I'll pull out
all of your fingernails!
[BOTH SCREAMING]
Isobel! [BREATH QUIVERS]
Oh my god!
Isobel!
[HUFFS]
That is not the kind of force
I was talking about!
Oh my god!
I'm just kidding!
You really think I can do that?!
Hm?
Anyway!
I was talking about
the Second Law.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
The acceleration of an object
is directly proportional
to the net force acting on it
and is inversely proportional
to its mass.
Oh! You mean...
more force?
- [APRIL WHIMPERS]
- [ISOBEL] Let's go, Dessalyn!
- Come here!
- [MUFFLED] No!
- [THWACKS]
- [APRIL CRIES]
- [DAPHNE LAUGHS]
- [ISOBEL] My turn!
- [APRIL CRYING]
- Hey! Put your hand in here!
- [APRIL CRYING] No! No! No!
- [DAPHNE LAUGHS]
Wait! Don't do it--
- [BUZZING, ZAPPING]
- [ISOBEL, DAPHNE CACKLING]
[NYX] Stop! Stop!
- Hey! Shh!
- [LAUGHTER DIES DOWN]
- Stop it!
- [ISOBEL, DAPHNE PANTING]
You guys are so morbid!
I cannot! Shh!
Calm down, okay?
- Calm down.
- [DAPHNE, ISOBEL HUFF]
You know...
let's just talk calmly.
Nothing can't be solved
with a good talk, right?
So, move.
Breathe! Breathe!
- Come on.
- [ISOBEL BREATHES DEEPLY]
Okay. Let's do this.
[CLEARS THROAT]
There. Mm.
Go ahead, breathe.
Inhale... Exhale.
Okay? Okay.
Okay, listen, girl.
We need your help.
Yes? Yes, okay.
Help us.
We need your powerful
hacking skills.
Let's take the boys down.
We believe in you.
And I promise... [CHUCKLES]
I'll treat you to some steak.
[GIGGLES]
[IN A CHILDISH VOICE] Yes? Yes!
I'll treat you to some steak.
- I'll treat you--
- [APRIL SPITS]
- [DAPHNE GASPS]
- [ISOBEL CHUCKLES]
Damn you!
Come here, you bitch!
[OVERLAPPING SCREAMING]
[MARLA]
Break it up! Stop it!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Order in the court!
- Okay! Okay!
- Good job!
Shush! Stop! Stop!
- Breathe, girls!
- I'm so proud of you.
Girls! Girls!
Stop, please! Please!
That is not how we're
gonna convince April!
- Yeah, then how?
- Calm down, okay?
Breathe! Everybody, breathe!
All together now!
- [GIRLS CLEARING THROATS]
- Okay, remember...
Remember the Third Law.
- [ISOBEL GROANS] Please.
- For every action...
...there is an equal
and opposite reaction.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay, so...
our force must come
from research.
Something needs to trigger
April so that she helps us.
Something...
Something has to happen.
[NYX CLEARS THROAT]
- Girl.
- Hm?
- Well...
- Yeah?
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- What?
What, you mean some kind
of divine intervention, huh?
[PHONES BUZZ, CHIME]
[APRIL GROANS]
You better stay there!
What?!
[MARLA HUFFS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FORCED CHUCKLE]
Is this a joke?!
Oh my god!
It's AI, obviously!
It's fake!
It's AI!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC TURNS TENSE]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[MUSIC FADES]
April?
[KNOCKS]
Are you okay?
Do you wanna get back
at the person
who leaked your nudes online?
- [NYX] Isobel.
- What?
Calm down.
She's still shocked.
Let her be.
I just don't wanna waste
my time. That's all.
She has a point.
Thanks.
[DAPHNE] Not you. Nyx.
[NYX] Just give her time.
April?
I'm not here to mess with you.
We're here...
to let you know
that there are people
who understand
what you're going through.
We might not understand
why this is happening to us...
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
But I know...
how important it is...
[SNIFFLES]
...to have someone
who understands you.
[SNIFFLES]
Whether it's a friend...
a stranger...
...or even an enemy.
What matters is that you
have someone to hold on to.
Because sometimes...
it's the only way
to feel less lonely.
She's not coming out.
Let's just go.
[CUBICLE DOOR CLOSES]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
What do you want from me?
[MUSIC BECOMES STIRRING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]